[{"answer": "I'm great.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "How are you doing, Piers?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "For sure.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "If you lose there, that's a big problem if you are presumed to be a frontrunner, right?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it just makes me laugh out loud.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "How do you answer that charge?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly think it's driven by the presence of Rick Santorum.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Why do you think that is and how will this play out?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "I have to correct that I served on a panel that President Bush appointed but I didn't work in his White House.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "What do you make of the current GOP race?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "I think that Romney has rendered himself unelectable in the general election and I think Rick Santorum, if he had stayed with the blue-collar narrative would have been much better off than heading into the religious rights territory that turns off moderates.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "So how effective is it to go carpet-bomb your opponents like this?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "I mean is that even a possibility, do you think?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, it's a horrible fact of life that money decides elections and that now after what the Republicans have done negative money with no limits can really corrupt the process.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Honestly, I explained that, you know, I feel like I am trying to create a dialogue and end this clash of civilization.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Be honest?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "He said, Allah be with you.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "So what did your -- what did your father say to that?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "My father made \"Alexander the Great,\" don't forget, who was a great unifier of people.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Your father said that?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "TONE: No.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "When you met him, did you bring up this denial of the Holocaust that he keeps purporting?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Do you stand by that?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "So you basically are defending the preventive war doctrine, which goes back to Bush.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Don't they have a right to feel vulnerable about that?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Because he's a fake.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "You have a new television ad that labels him a fake, why?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I don't think the party has a clue who is going to be the nominee, after watching last night.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I couldn't agree with you more that he's taken the exact wrong tack on this.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Is this a debate they should be having, given that the rest of America is screaming about jobs and the economy?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I don't think that it was the candidates so much that wanted to focus on these issues.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Is there a danger that this particular obsessive debate with social conservative issues is just going to make them look rather out of touch with modern America?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Carol Roth, I mean, Mitt Romney is still I guess de facto the front-runner.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "You can even take that a step further, which is how many more mandates might there be buried in Obamacare?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "The problem with Mitt Romney is the same problem that all the candidates had last night.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "What is the problem for Mitt Romney, do you think?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "It would be a disaster.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "If he was to lose in Michigan, then that's bad for him, isn't it?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, I think it is because, of course, it's all of those states in contention that night.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Super Tuesday is going to be the really big indicator as to whether Mitt Romney can become a proper front-runner, isn't it?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "I totally agree.", "docId": "120223pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "That's not coming across in these debates?", "qSentId": 581}]